tutorialsphere.com 2011-11-27

# Privacy - Tutorialsphere.com

## Registration

In order to use this website to the full potential, we highly recommend you to first complete the registration form. During registration a user is required to give their username, name, password, e-mail address, and other personal information. This information is to identify the user, and for other users to interact with the user. None of this information will be sold, transmitted, or in any other way sent to any third parties. You also may be asked for your location, instant messenger names, etc but these are only optional and you may leave them empty. We also record data like ip for security reasons only and they are not available to other users. 

## Cookies

Cookies are used to identify the user when he/she logs in, and for tracking purposes. A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user’s hard drive containing information about the user. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. First type of cookies is: once the user closes their browser, the cookie simply terminates. Second type becomes active when the user selects the checkbox “Remember me” from the login form. This cookie stores on your computer to keep you logged in, even after you close your browser and remembers your information so that you won't have to enter it again every time you visit our site. 

## Passwords

Our staff will NEVER ask for your password. If someone does ask for your password or other info, please immediately notify us. 

## Log Files

We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information. 

## Links

This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that Tutorialsphere.com is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this website. 

## Notification of Changes

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on the news so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by way of an e-mail. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.

If you have any questions regarding our privacy policy, please do not hesitate to [contact us](http://www.tutorialsphere.com/contact). Thank you for your cooperation.
